

Chetan Jain

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

A web developer with over 2 years of experience in the industry. I have a keen eye for layout and design, and I'm passionate about building highly optimized user-friendly websites. I have experience in both front-end and back-end development, and I'm comfortable working with a variety of programming languages.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date 25/03/1998

Nationality

Indian

CONTACT

- jain.cj.chetan@gmail.com
- +91-8700776723
- thechetanjain.in
- iginchetan81
- jainChetan81

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

UNOLO | FIELD FORCE MANAGEMENT

04-2021 - NOW

I was responsible for developing and maintaining the Admin Panel of the company website from scratch which is essential for Company's revenue. My duties included working with the back-end developers to ensure that all the new and legacy functionalities of the website were functioning properly. I also took care of all the functional and visual aspects of the website design, including layout, colors, and graphics. Additionally, I oversaw the testing of the website to ensure that it was compatible with all major browsers.

Front End Developer L1

AXENO CONSULTING

02-2020 - 04-2021

My role was working on both the front-end and back-end of web applications, as well as developing new features and maintaining existing ones. I also collaborated closely with other team members, such as designers and front-end developers, to ensure that the final product was of the highest quality.

EDUCATION

BTech + MTech (Computer Science)

JAYPEE INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY

2016 - 2021

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Typescript	CSS3	HTML5	React	Svelte	MySql	tRPC	PWA	Unit Testing
------------	------	-------	-------	--------	-------	------	-----	--------------

PROJECTS

Recreated Google Forms with all functionalities and a working backend and deployed at chetanexamples.vercel.app/dynamic_form Created a tree like Organization Chart for Multiple role based Managers and deployed at chetan-examples.vercel.app/react_flow